<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pc version="5">
<character><name>Tallguy McClean-Shaven</name><race><source>1</source><name>Hill Dwarf</name><speed>25</speed><feat><name>Languages</name><text>You can speak, read, and write Common and Dwarvish. Dwarvish is full of hard consonants and guttural sounds, and those characteristics spill over into whatever other language a dwarf might speak.</text></feat><feat><name>Darkvision</name><text>Accustomed to life underground, you have superior vision in dark and dim conditions. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.</text></feat><feat><name>Dwarven Resilience</name><text>You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage.</text></feat><feat><name>Dwarven Combat Training</name><text>You have proficiency with the battleaxe, handaxe, light hammer, and warhammer.</text></feat><feat><name>Tool Proficiency</name><text>You gain proficiency with the artisan’s tools of your choice: smith’s tools, brewer’s supplies, or mason’s tools.</text></feat><feat><name>Stonecunning</name><text>Whenever you make an Intelligence (History) check related to the origin of stonework, you are considered proficient in the History skill and add double your proficiency bonus to the check, instead of your normal proficiency bonus.</text></feat><feat><name>Dwarven Toughness</name><text>Your hit point maximum increases by 1, and it increases by 1 every time you gain a level.</text></feat><mod><category>1</category><type>2</type><value>2</value></mod><mod><category>1</category><type>4</type><value>1</value></mod></race>
<class><source>1</source><id>1008</id><name>Cleric</name><level>8</level><hd>2</hd><hdCurrent>8</hdCurrent><spellAbility>4</spellAbility><slots>4,4,3,3,2,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><slotsCurrent>4,4,3,3,2,0,0,0,0,0,</slotsCurrent><spell><source>1</source><name>Thaumaturgy</name><school>8</school><time>1 action</time><range>30 feet</range><components>V</components><duration>Up to 1 minute</duration><text>You manifest a minor wonder, a sign of supernatural power, within range. You create one of the following magical effects within
    Range:
• Your voice booms up to three times as loud as normal for 1 minute.
• You cause flames to flicker, brighten, dim, or change color for 1 minute.
• You cause harmless tremors in the ground for 1 minute.
• You create an instantaneous sound that originates from a point of your choice within range, such as a rumble of thunder, the cry of a raven, or ominous whispers.
• You instantaneously cause an unlocked door or window to fly open or slam shut.
• You alter the appearance of your eyes for 1 minute.
    If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its 1 minute effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</text><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Sacred Flame</name><school>5</school><time>1 action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>Flame like radiance descends on a creature that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or take 1d8 radiant damage. The target gains no benefit from cover for this saving throw.
    The spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</text><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Cure Wounds</name><level>1</level><school>5</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass><sclass>Ranger</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Create or Destroy Water</name><level>1</level><school>8</school><time>1 action</time><range>30 feet</range><components>V, S, M (a drop of water if creating water or a few grains of sand if destroying it)</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>You either create or destroy water.
    Create Water. You create up to 10 gallons of clean water within range in an open container. Alternatively, the water falls as rain in a 30 foot cube within range, extinguishing exposed flames in the area.
    Destroy Water. You destroy up to 10 gallons of water in an open container within range. Alternatively, you destroy fog in a 30 foot cube within range.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you create or destroy 10 additional gallons of water, or the size of the cube increases by 5 feet, for each slot level above 1st.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Hold Person</name><level>2</level><school>4</school><time>1 action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components><duration>Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration><text>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass><sclass>Sorcerer</sclass><sclass>Warlock</sclass><sclass>Wizard</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Light</name><school>5</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, M (a firefly or phosphorescent moss)</components><duration>1 hour</duration><text>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright light in a 20 foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely covering the object with something opaque blocks the light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it as an action.
    If you target an object held or worn by a hostile creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw to avoid the spell.</text><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Sorcerer</sclass><sclass>Wizard</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Mass Healing Word</name><level>3</level><school>5</school><time>1 bonus action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>As you call out words of restoration, up to six creatures of your choice that you can see within range regain hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 3rd.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Calm Emotions</name><level>2</level><school>4</school><time>1 action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration><text>You attempt to suppress strong emotions in a group of people. Each humanoid in a 20 foot radius sphere centered on a point you choose within range must make a Charisma saving throw; a creature can choose to fail this saving throw if it wishes. If a creature fails its saving throw, choose one of the following two effects.
    You can suppress any effect causing a target to be charmed or frightened. When this spell ends, any suppressed effect resumes, provided that its duration has not expired in the meantime.
    Alternatively, you can make a target indifferent about creatures of your choice that it is hostile toward. This indifference ends if the target is attacked or harmed by a spell or if it witnesses any of its friends being harmed. When the spell ends, the creature becomes hostile again, unless the GM rules otherwise.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><name>Guardian of Faith</name><level>4</level><time>1 action</time><range>30 feet</range><components>V</components><duration>8 hours</duration><text>    A large spectral guardian appears and hovers for the duration in an unoccupied space of your choice that you can see within range.  The guardian occupies that space and is indistinct except for a gleaming sword and shield emblazoned with the symbol of your deity.
    Any creature hostile to you that moves to a space within 10 feet of the guardian for the first time on a turn must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw.  The creature takes 20 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.  The guardian vanishes when it has dealt a total of 60 damage.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Resistance</name><school>1</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, S, M (a miniature cloak)</components><duration>Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration><text>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one saving throw of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the saving throw. The spell then ends.</text><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Spirit Guardians</name><level>3</level><school>2</school><time>1 action</time><range>Self (15 foot radius)</range><components>V, S, M (a holy symbol)</components><duration>Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration><text>You call forth spirits to protect you. They flit around you to a distance of 15 feet for the duration. If you are good or neutral, their spectral form appears angelic or fey (your choice). If you are evil, they appear fiendish.
    When you cast this spell, you can designate any number of creatures you can see to be unaffected by it. An affected creature’s speed is halved in the area, and when the creature enters the area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature takes 3d8 radiant damage (if you are good or neutral) or 3d8 necrotic damage (if you are evil). On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 3rd.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Zone of Truth</name><level>2</level><school>4</school><time>1 action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V, S</components><duration>10 minutes</duration><text>You create a magical zone that guards against deception in a 15 foot radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range. Until the spell ends, a creature that enters the spell’s area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there must make a Charisma saving throw. On a failed save, a creature can’t speak a deliberate lie while in the radius. You know whether each creature succeeds or fails on its saving throw.
    An affected creature is aware of the spell and can thus avoid answering questions to which it would normally respond with a lie. Such a creature can be evasive in its answers as long as it remains within the boundaries of the truth.</text><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Detect Magic</name><level>1</level><school>3</school><ritual>1</ritual><time>1 action</time><range>Self</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration><text>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.
    The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass><sclass>Ranger</sclass><sclass>Sorcerer</sclass><sclass>Wizard</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Beacon of Hope</name><level>3</level><school>1</school><time>1 action</time><range>30 feet</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration><text>This spell bestows hope and vitality. Choose any number of creatures within range. For the duration, each target has advantage on Wisdom saving throws and death saving throws, and regains the maximum number of hit points possible from any healing.</text><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Shield of Faith</name><level>1</level><school>1</school><time>1 bonus action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V, S, M (a small parchment with a bit of holy text written on it)</components><duration>Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration><text>A shimmering field appears and surrounds a creature of your choice within range, granting it a +2 bonus to AC for the duration.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Spiritual Weapon</name><level>2</level><school>5</school><time>1 bonus action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V, S</components><duration>1 minute</duration><text>You create a floating, spectral weapon within range that lasts for the duration or until you cast this spell again. When you cast the spell, you can make a melee spell attack against a creature within 5 feet of the weapon. On a hit, the target takes force damage equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier.
    As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the weapon up to 20 feet and repeat the attack against a creature within 5 feet of it.
    The weapon can take whatever form you choose. Clerics of deities who are associated with a particular weapon (as St. Cuthbert is known for his mace and Thor for his hammer) make this spell’s effect resemble that weapon.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for every two slot levels above 2nd.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Death Ward</name><level>4</level><school>1</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, S</components><duration>8 hours</duration><text>You touch a creature and grant it a measure of protection from death.
    The first time the target would drop to 0 hit points as a result of taking damage, the target instead drops to 1 hit point, and the spell ends.
    If the spell is still in effect when the target is subjected to an effect that would kill it instantaneously without dealing damage, that effect is instead negated against the target, and the spell ends.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Revivify</name><level>3</level><school>7</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, S, M (diamonds worth 300 gp, which the spell consumes)</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>You touch a creature that has died within the last minute. That creature returns to life with 1 hit point. This spell can’t return to life a creature that has died of old age, nor can it restore any missing body parts.</text><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Bless</name><level>1</level><school>4</school><time>1 action</time><range>30 feet</range><components>V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components><duration>Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration><text>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Guiding Bolt</name><level>1</level><school>5</school><time>1 action</time><range>120 feet</range><components>V, S</components><duration>1 round</duration><text>A flash of light streaks toward a creature of your choice within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 4d6 radiant damage, and the next attack roll made against this target before the end of your next turn has advantage, thanks to the mystical dim light glittering on the target until then.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Inflict Wounds</name><level>1</level><school>7</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>Make a melee spell attack against a creature you can reach. On a hit, the target takes 3d10 necrotic damage.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 1st.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Cleric</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Lesser Restoration</name><level>2</level><school>1</school><time>1 action</time><range>Touch</range><components>V, S</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</text><prepared>1</prepared><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass><sclass>Paladin</sclass><sclass>Ranger</sclass></spell><spell><source>1</source><name>Healing Word</name><level>1</level><school>5</school><time>1 bonus action</time><range>60 feet</range><components>V</components><duration>Instantaneous</duration><text>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.
    At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</text><sclass>Bard</sclass><sclass>Cleric</sclass><sclass>Druid</sclass></spell><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Bonus Proficiency</name><text>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain proficiency with heavy armor.</text></feat><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Disciple of Life</name><text>Also starting at 1st level, your healing spells are more effective. Whenever you use a spell of 1st level or higher to restore hit points to a creature, the creature regains additional hit points equal to 2+the spell&#39;s level.</text></feat><feat><name>Channel Divinity</name><text>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to channel divine energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some domains grant you additional effects as you advance in levels, as noted in the domain description.
    When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.
    Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your cleric spell save DC.
    Beginning at 6th level, you can use your Channel Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at 18th level. you can use it three times between rests. When you finish a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.</text></feat><feat><name>Channel Divinity: Turn Undead</name><text>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring the undead. Each undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.
    A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can’t willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can’t take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there’s nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</text></feat><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain Channel Divinity: Preserve Life</name><text>Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity to heal the badly injured.
    As an action, you present your holy symbol and evoke healing energy that can restore a number of hit points equal to five times your cleric level. Choose any creatures within 30 feet of you, and divide those hit points among them. This feature can restore a creature to no more than half of its hit point maximum. You can&#39;t use this feature on an undead or a construct.</text></feat><feat><name>Destroy Undead</name><text>Starting at 5th level, when an undead fails its saving throw against your Turn Undead feature, the creature is instantly destroyed if its challenge rating is at or below a certain threshold, as shown in the Destroy Undead table.
Cleric Level Destroys Undead of CR
5th 1/2 or lower
8th 1 or lower
11th 2 or lower
14th 3 or lower
17th 4 or lower</text><expanded>0</expanded></feat><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Blessed Healer</name><text>Beginning at 6th level, the healing spells you cast on others heal you as well. When you cast a spell of 1st level or higher that restores hit points to a creature other than you, you regain hit points equal to 2+the spell&#39;s level.</text></feat><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Divine Strike</name><text>At 8th level, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with divine energy. Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can cause the attack to deal an extra 1d8 radiant damage to the target. When you reach 14th level, the extra damage increases to 2d8.</text></feat><proficiency>109</proficiency><proficiency>114</proficiency><proficiency>107</proficiency><proficiency>103</proficiency><proficiency>5</proficiency><proficiency>4</proficiency><autolevel><slots>3,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Bonus Proficiency</name><text>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain proficiency with heavy armor.</text></feat><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Disciple of Life</name><text>Also starting at 1st level, your healing spells are more effective. Whenever you use a spell of 1st level or higher to restore hit points to a creature, the creature regains additional hit points equal to 2+the spell&#39;s level.</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>2</level><slots>3,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><feat><name>Channel Divinity</name><text>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to channel divine energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some domains grant you additional effects as you advance in levels, as noted in the domain description.
    When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.
    Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your cleric spell save DC.
    Beginning at 6th level, you can use your Channel Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at 18th level. you can use it three times between rests. When you finish a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.</text></feat><feat><name>Channel Divinity: Turn Undead</name><text>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring the undead. Each undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.
    A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can’t willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can’t take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there’s nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</text></feat><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain Channel Divinity: Preserve Life</name><text>Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity to heal the badly injured.
    As an action, you present your holy symbol and evoke healing energy that can restore a number of hit points equal to five times your cleric level. Choose any creatures within 30 feet of you, and divide those hit points among them. This feature can restore a creature to no more than half of its hit point maximum. You can&#39;t use this feature on an undead or a construct.</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>3</level><slots>3,4,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>4</level><slots>4,4,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>5</level><slots>4,4,3,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><feat><name>Destroy Undead</name><text>Starting at 5th level, when an undead fails its saving throw against your Turn Undead feature, the creature is instantly destroyed if its challenge rating is at or below a certain threshold, as shown in the Destroy Undead table.
Cleric Level Destroys Undead of CR
5th 1/2 or lower
8th 1 or lower
11th 2 or lower
14th 3 or lower
17th 4 or lower</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>6</level><slots>4,4,3,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Blessed Healer</name><text>Beginning at 6th level, the healing spells you cast on others heal you as well. When you cast a spell of 1st level or higher that restores hit points to a creature other than you, you regain hit points equal to 2+the spell&#39;s level.</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>7</level><slots>4,4,3,3,1,0,0,0,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>8</level><slots>4,4,3,3,2,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Divine Strike</name><text>At 8th level, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with divine energy. Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can cause the attack to deal an extra 1d8 radiant damage to the target. When you reach 14th level, the extra damage increases to 2d8.</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>9</level><slots>4,4,3,3,3,1,0,0,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>10</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,0,0,0,0,</slots><feat><name>Divine Intervention</name><text>Beginning at 10th level, you can call on your deity to intervene on your behalf when your need is great.
    Imploring your deity’s aid requires you to use your action. Describe the assistance you seek, and roll percentile dice. If you roll a number equal to or lower than your cleric level, your deity intervenes. The DM chooses the nature of the intervention; the effect of any cleric spell or cleric domain spell would be appropriate. If your deity intervenes, you can’t use this feature again for 7 days. Otherwise, you can use it again after you finish a long rest.
    At 20th level, your call for intervention succeeds automatically, no roll required.</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>11</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,0,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>12</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,0,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>13</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,1,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>14</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,1,0,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>15</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,1,1,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>16</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,1,1,0,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>17</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,2,1,1,1,1,</slots><feat><optional>1</optional><name>Life Domain: Supreme Healing</name><text>Starting at 17th level, when you would normally roll one or more dice to restore hit points with a spell, you instead use the highest number possible for each die. For example, instead of restoring 2d6 hit points to a creature, you restore 12.</text></feat></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>18</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,3,1,1,1,1,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>19</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,3,2,1,1,1,</slots></autolevel>
<autolevel><level>20</level><slots>5,4,3,3,3,3,2,2,1,1,</slots></autolevel>
</class>

<background></background>
<xp>40955</xp>
<abilities>14,8,15,10,17,12,</abilities>
<hpMax>71</hpMax><hpCurrent>71</hpCurrent><hpTemp>0</hpTemp>
<item><name>Chain mail dragon fire</name><type>3</type><weight>55</weight><ac>16</ac><strength>13</strength><stealth>1</stealth></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Shield</name><type>4</type><slot>4</slot><weight>6</weight><ac>2</ac></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Handaxe</name><type>5</type><quantity>0</quantity><weight>2</weight><damage1H>1d6</damage1H><damageType>3</damageType><weaponProperty>136</weaponProperty><weaponRange>20</weaponRange><weaponLongRange>60</weaponLongRange><mod><type>1</type></mod></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Handaxe</name><type>5</type><quantity>0</quantity><weight>2</weight><damage1H>1d6</damage1H><damageType>3</damageType><weaponProperty>136</weaponProperty><weaponRange>20</weaponRange><weaponLongRange>60</weaponLongRange><mod><type>1</type></mod></item>
<item><name>Holy Symbol</name><weight>0</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Backpack</name><weight>5</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Crowbar</name><text>Using a crowbar grants advantage to Strength checks where the crowbar’s leverage can be applied.</text><weight>5</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Hammer</name><weight>3</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Piton</name><quantity>9</quantity><weight>0.25</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Tinderbox</name><text>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch—or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel—takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</text><weight>1</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Rations (1 day)</name><text>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</text><quantity>8</quantity><weight>2</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Torch</name><text>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</text><quantity>10</quantity><weight>1</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Gold (gp)</name><type>15</type><quantity>3411</quantity><weight>0.02</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Waterskin</name><weight>5</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Hempen rope (50 feet)</name><text>Rope, whether made of hemp or silk, has 2 hit points and can be burst with a DC 17 Strength check.</text><quantity>0</quantity><weight>10</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Mason&#39;s tools</name><weight>8</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Common clothes</name><weight>3</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Pouch</name><text>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</text><weight>1</weight></item>
<item><name>Rank Insignia </name><weight>0</weight></item>
<item><name>Deck of playing cards</name><weight>0</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Potion of healing</name><text>A character who drinks the magical red fluid in this vial regains 2d4 + 2 hit points. Drinking or administering a potion takes an action.</text><weight>0.5</weight></item>
<item><name>Hugh + 1</name><type>5</type><slot>2</slot><weight>4</weight><damage1H>1d8</damage1H><damage2H>1d10</damage2H><damageType>3</damageType><weaponProperty>512</weaponProperty><mod><type>1</type></mod></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Silver (sp)</name><type>15</type><quantity>926</quantity><weight>0.02</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Heavy crossbow</name><type>6</type><weight>18</weight><damage1H>1d10</damage1H><damageType>2</damageType><weaponProperty>277</weaponProperty><weaponRange>100</weaponRange><weaponLongRange>400</weaponLongRange><mod><type>1</type></mod></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Electrum (ep)</name><type>15</type><quantity>441</quantity><weight>0.02</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Copper (cp)</name><type>15</type><quantity>0</quantity><weight>0.02</weight></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Platinum (pp)</name><type>15</type><quantity>46</quantity><weight>0.02</weight></item>
<item><name>Lightbringer+1</name><text>1d6 radiant against undead</text><type>5</type><weight>4</weight><damage1H>1d6</damage1H><damageType>1</damageType><mod><type>1</type></mod></item>
<item><source>1</source><name>Plate Armor</name><type>3</type><slot>5</slot><weight>65</weight><ac>18</ac><strength>15</strength><stealth>1</stealth></item>
<item><name>Rope (100 ft)</name><quantity>6</quantity><weight>7</weight></item>
<item><name>Chys gemstone</name><quantity>6</quantity><weight>0.1</weight></item>
<item><name>large onyx</name><quantity>4</quantity><weight>1</weight></item>
<item><name>Potion of greater healing</name><quantity>2</quantity><weight>0.5</weight></item>
<item><name>Agot</name><text>10 gold each</text><quantity>6</quantity><weight>2</weight></item>
<item><name>Silver pitcher </name><text>Found in crushing wave cult house</text><quantity>0</quantity><weight>0</weight></item>
<item><name>50 dwarvin books</name><text>Found in water cult house</text><weight>0</weight></item>
<tracker><label>Bolts</label><type>0</type><value>4</value><formula>20</formula></tracker>
<tracker><label>Spirit</label><value>7</value><formula>10</formula></tracker>
<tracker><label>Bless</label><value>10</value><formula>10</formula></tracker>
<note><name>+20 health </name><expanded>0</expanded><archived>1</archived></note>
<note><name>Mishakal</name><text>LG, blue infinity symbol </text><expanded>1</expanded><archived>0</archived></note>
</character></pc>